Hey Leila, how are you doing?
Hey Nate, not great to be honest.
This round of layoffs is making me nervous.
I can relate. It's a stressful time.
Are you looking at other jobs?
I'm trying, but I haven't had much luck.
I need to find a different job
where I won't be as replaceable.
All my experience has been
in customer service, unfortunately.
I have no idea what employers
are even looking for.
The last time I was shifting careers,
my former manager recommended
that I proactively sign up for courses
and certifications to learn different skill sets.
That's interesting.
What kind of skills did you learn?
Everything ranging from thinking critically
to structuring my communication.
These skills are crucial to any career,
and typically what most employers are looking for.
And why you have to learn other skills,
which can certainly be challenging.
Keeping your successes in mind
can help you through the tough times.
This is very helpful.
I did see an opening for a computer user support
specialist that would allow me to work remotely,
but I'm hesitant to apply.
Why is that?
To be honest, I feel overwhelmed
and slightly resentful towards technology.
It seems like it's always changing
and I can never keep up.
Learning how you can work and think in new ways with
data and technology will not only remove barriers,
but it will put you in a great place
to apply for this role.
Of course, you'll need to continue
expanding your digital skills,
but a good foundation will get you
started to keep learning.